<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.typora.Typora</id>
  <name>Typora</name>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://support.typora.io/License-Agreement/</project_license>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <summary>A minimal Markdown reading &amp; writing app</summary>
  <developer id="io.typora">
    <name>Typora</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>
      Typora gives you a seamless experience as both a reader and a writer. It removes the preview window, mode switcher, syntax symbols of markdown source code, and all other unnecessary distractions. Instead, it provides a real live preview feature to help you concentrate on the content itself.
    </p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.typora.Typora.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://typora.io/img/theme-prev/Snip20141101_3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://typora.io/img/new/image.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://typora.io/img/new/toc.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://typora.io/img/new/lists.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://typora.io/img/new/table.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://typora.io/img/new/fences.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://typora.io/img/new/math.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://typora.io/img/new/diagram.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://typora.io/img/new/inline.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://typora.io/img/new/etc.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://typora.io/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://support.typora.io/</url>
  <url type="help">https://support.typora.io/</url>

  <provides>
    <binary>typora</binary>
  </provides>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.11.7" date="2025-08-31">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix generated markdown link when drop video files into Typora.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.11.5" date="2025-08-19">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix print dialog not show for print operations on Windows / Linux.
          Other bug fix.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.11.4" date="2025-08-16">
      <description>
        <p>
          New Features
            LaTeX Delimiters Support. Added support for \(...\) (inline math) and \[...\] (block math).
            Move Row/Paragraph Up/Down using Alt + ↑ / ↓ to move.
            Mermaid v11.7 Update with new diagram types supported:
              Radar Chart (radar-beta)
              Treemap (treemap-beta)

          Improvements
            Exported HTML now includes Zenuml CSS only when needed (smaller file size).
            Improved math compatibility when pasting from ChatGPT and AI tools.
            Styles preserved when copying to WeChat Official Accounts.
            “Copy without theme styling” now respects plain text setting.
            Videos dropped into Typora now include the controls attribute.
            Exported images no longer use referrerPolicy='no-referrer' by default.
            Option added to disable emoji autocomplete when typing :.
            Improve UI translations for Slovenian, Chinese, Dutch, Polish, Norwegian Nynorsk, French, Portuguese and Swedish.

          Linux Updates
          Replaced old APT key using SHA1 with a new secure one. Follow support.typora.io/What's-New-1.11/#linux for more details
            Improved Wayland compatibility. Follow support.typora.io/What's-New-1.11/#wayland for more details

          Bug Fixes
            Fixed text clipping in PDF exports.
            Fixed Mermaid code not working on macOS 12.
            Fixed --- not rendering properly.
            Prevented unwanted indentation when “Indent first line of paragraph” is enabled.
            Fixed issue where GIFs from clipboard couldn’t be inserted.
            Fixed list paste issues in some cases.
            Fixed missing list bullets after 999+ items.
            Fixed PDF export glitches on macOS.
            Fixed issue where outline filter panel closed unexpectedly after scroll.
            Zoom setting with mouse wheel now preserved.
            Fixed rendering issues for certain code blocks with url mode.
            Fix sort naturally in files sidebar.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.10.8" date="2025-02-27">
      <description>
        <p>
          Support math expressions pasted from ChatGPT or other AI services.
          Fix linux installer on older Debian system.
          Fix pickiest not displayed in some languages.
          Fix image not inserted after confirm dialog is shown.
          Fix PDF export when custom margin is set.
          Fix checkbox for Articles and File Tree under View menu is not exclusive.
          Other Bug fixes.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.10.6" date="2025-02-20">
      <description>
        <p>
          Improvements
            Mermaid is now upgrade to 11.4, with new diagrams including:
              Packet Diagram
              Kanban Diagram
              Architecture Diagrams
            Update translations for Danish, Hindi and Vietnamese.
            Better PDF export on Windows / Linux: Able to export to PDF with dark themes and keep the background.
            Toggle alert from View menu now follows the same logic as blockquote, which means you can select a range of paragraph and changes them into Github Alert from Paragraph → Alert from menubar.
            Add gas syntax highlight, in previous version, gas will be treated as alias of assembly incorrectly.
            Add url syntax highlight.
            The image uploader option, piclist, is applied on all languages.
            Fix syntax switch for images failed in some cases.
            Allow users to drag-and-drop / insert images with jiff extension.
            Do not escape image url with http protocol.

          Fix
            Fix window fullscreen / maximize state not restored on Typora restart.
            Allow scroll the side mega menu panel when zoomed under Windows.
            Fix file contains some emojis are not detected as UTF-8 encode
            Fix select lists items and toggle list type be applied on wrong blocks.
            Fix typing on last line of code block may make the app hangs.
            Fix adding anchor link to headings with “+” character not work correctly after export.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.9.3" date="2024-06-21">
      <description>
        <p>
          New
            Support gitlab style math code block.
            Upgrade mermaid 10.9.1, Block Diagrams are now supported.

          Improvements
            Follow CommonMark rule to handle whitespace inside code.
            Improve scroll performance, improve performance on macOS 14.
            Shorten file path in open recent menu.
            “Inspect Element” on macOS moved from context menu to Sfarai Develop menu.
            New file on file tree no longer need confirm after input its filename.
            Add structured text code syntax highlight.
            Chapter levels can be configured for ePub export.
            Update languages in Polish, Traditional Chinese, Slovenian, Czech and Norwegian Nynorsk.

          Fix
            Fix Javascript XSS on mermaid and math.
            Fix anchor id when export.
            Fix bookmark for exported PDF cannot be shown in Adobe Reader.
            Fix some remote images cannot be loaded on macOS.
            Fix “&amp;” not displayed for file path contains “&amp;” In “recent files” menu on Windows / Linux.
            Fix “$” in code language name leads to a wrong string.
            Other bug fix.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.8.9" date="2024-01-29">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix search in preferences panel.
          Fix install and export issue on Linux.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.8.6" date="2024-01-24">
      <description>
        <p>
          N/A
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.8.5" date="2024-01-19">
      <description>
        <p>
          New
            Add support for Github style alerts / callouts.
            Add option to enable zoom with command or ctrl key and mouse wheel.
            Upgrade mermaid library with XY charts support.

          Improvements
            Linux version now also support separate theme for light and dark mode.
            Quicker way to add “New Markdown” menu item in Windows Explorer
            Now, typora uses mermaid's own dark theme when rendering mermaid in dark mode.
            Improve performance and stability.
            Update translation for Spanish, French, Galician, Slovenian, Vietnamese and Chinese.
            Add Norwegian Nynorsk language interface.

          Bug Fix
            Fix window position in multiple monitor.
            Fix save as image for diagrams.
            Hide “copy as HTML” for unsupported blocks.
            Add “copy as HTML” support for mermaid diagrams.
            Fix “PicList not found” error when using PicList to upload images.
            Fix cursor misplaced when editing emoji.
            Fix issues on image syntax parse and convert.
            Other bug fix.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.7.6" date="2023-11-01">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix "save as" logic on Windows / Linux.
          Improve activation network for users in China mainland.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.7.5" date="2023-09-21">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix code signing on macOS.
          Fix security issues, including CVE-2023-4863.
          Fix search in preferences panel.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.7.4" date="2023-09-09">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix search in preferences panel.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.7.3" date="2023-09-06">
      <description>
        <p>
          New
            Upgrade mermaid to 10.3.1, supports Sankey diagrams and Quadrant Chart.
            Add menu item to open outline popover (macOS) and Wordcount popover.
            Larger scrollbar when hover on Windows/ Linux.
            Add Modelica language syntax support.
            Add delete diagram option in context menu.
            Add options to not save recent folders / files.
            Add buttons to pin and remove recent folders from sidebar panel.
            Add variable ${outputFolder} and ${outputFolderName}

          Improvements and Fix
            Better paste list from Apple Notes.
            Improve open file with anchor locations.
            Fix sort order not saved after restart Typora.
            Header and footers now respect page margins when export to PDF.
            Fix exporting ordered list when using theme Whitey.
            typora-root-url now supports absolute image path on Windows.
            Fix filename suggestion is improper when first heading is under editing.
            Fix indent in code blocks not kept when paste into other web apps on macOS.
            Non-exist #anchor links is now preserved.
            Disable alert in embeded iframes.
            Fix shortcut key for upload image cannot be set.
            Fix drag files from file sidebar on some Linux distributions.
            Fix app not responsive when do line-wise cut on empty line.
            Fix some issues about cut line.
            Fix indent issue when indent paragraph is enabled on macOS ≥ 13
            Fix improper behavior when press shift + arrow key then press arrow key on macOS.
            Fix typo of the menu item for Greek encoding option on Windows / Linux.
            Fix code language autocomplete not work for ~~~.
            Fix security issue STAR-2023-0062
            Add menu item of “jump to line start”, fix Ctrl + A/E on macOS.
            Add batch as alias of BAT in code language selector.
            Fix some meta data on YAML not get read or applied on export.
            Fix cursor jump after :emoji:.
            Fix shift + down on task lists.
            Fix checkbox style on macOS.
            Fix anchor link related issues.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.6.6" date="2023-05-22">
      <description>
        <p>
          Breaking Changes
            The Windows version no longer support Windows 7, 8, 8.1.

          Better Preferences Panel
            Add "Files" section and retune Preferences Panel.
            Add options to set default file extension.
            Add options to control behavior when drop file or folder into Typora.
            Add options to disable auto link.
            Add options to set default code language when inserting code blocks.
            Add options to auto apply last used code language when inserting code blocks.

          Other New Features
            Support Timeline for MermaidJS diagrams.
            Add Thai Language UI.
            Add PicList as an Image Uploader.
            Add PEG.js syntax highlight support.

          Other Improvements
            Fix CVE-2023-2317.
            Fix CVE-2023-2316.
            Avoid using google font mirrors in exported HTML, now official google font CDN is used.
            using keyword["keyword"] sometimes causes node not rendered in Mermaid diagram.
            color of typic package not readable in dark themes.
            setting inline mermaid configs may also affect other mermaid blocks.
            tasks status cannot be changed from menu bar when task list is under nested lists.
            math block is always auto numbered in exported docx and related setting is ignored.
            [Spec change] Typora now allow users to escape : mark to avoid input unwanted emoji codes.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.10" date="2023-03-24">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix selection range after insert image.
          Fix cursor when typing inside styled links.
          Fix find again after switch docs.
          Fix use command line typora aaa.md when aaa.md does not exists.
          Fix garbled path under open recent menu.
          Fix PDF export contains page break div.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.9" date="2023-03-14">
      <description>
        <p>
          Add option to switch Shift+Tab behavior between outdent and auto indent inside code blocks.
          Add menu and context menu to copy all code contents.
          Add menu and context menu to auto indent code contents.
          Fix sort in file tree not saved.
          Fix compatibility issue with Pandoc 3.0
          Other bug fixes.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.8" date="2023-02-15">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix the behavior of opening folder in Typora.
          Fix create new file in file tree.
          Fix footer and header for exported PDF.
          Other bug fix.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.6" date="2023-02-09">
      <description>
        <p>
          Small bug fix.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.5.5" date="2023-02-06">
      <description>
        <p>
          Code Block / Source Code Mode
            Add yara code syntax highlight.
            Add svelte code syntax highlight.
            Improve syntax highlight for SQL.
            Fix input in language input of code blocks when using IME.
            Fix cut not save data to clipboard when on text is selected but line wise copy cut is enabled.
            Shift + Tab will outdent selected contents in code block and source code mode.
            Recognize the end of code blocks in markdown source code mode.
            Improve syntax highlight of links in markdown source code mode.
            Fix continuous list when press Enter key in source code mode.

          Code Block / Source Code Mode
            Upgrade mermaid version to 9.2 which brings bug fix and Mindmaps

          UI / UX
            Change some button labels.
            Images supports float in custom CSS.
            Fix wrong scroll on code blocks when clicking global search result.
            Fix word break for code in outlines.
            In list list view, #test in file summary will be treated as normal text or heading texts, depends on the option of “Strict Mode” for markdown parsing rules in preferences panel.
            Fix global search not correctly highlight text in table.
            Fix create new tab may cause Typora window loose focus on macOS

          Import / Export
            Image export now support quantity options.
            Use local font, instead of remote font when exporting PDF.
            Highlight is supported and converted when export to LaTeX.
            Improve spacing in lists when export to PDF or images.
            Follow Pandoc’s way to export task list when target is docx, out, or rtf.
            Generate more readable title for Epub export.

          Editing
            Allow open local file link contains “#” in file path.
            Improve paste results from Google Docs.
            HTML entities are now case sensitive.

          Windows
            This version supports Windows 7 again. Now Typora subscribe to different update channel on Windows 7 and newer Windows versions.
            Link url starts like C:/ will also be recognized as absolute path, in previous versions, only path like D:\ will be treated as absolute url on Windows.
            Better restore icon for unibody style.
            Fix loading images from WSL path and net drivers.

          I18n
            Add new UI language: Norwegian
            Update language translation of Slovenian, Vietnamese, Chinese.

          Others
            Update description message for deb package.
            Other bug fix.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.8" date="2022-10-11">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix open Folder.
          Fix issues about page break for PDF export.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.6" date="2022-09-11">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix save file dialog not show for snap and flathub package.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.4" date="2022-09-05">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix scroll for code block not displayed in some cases.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.4.3" date="2022-09-05">
      <description>
        <p>
          New
            Upgrade mermaid version. Support inline mermaid configs.
            Upgrade mathjax version.
            Add copy as image option for math and diagrams.
            Add option to mix files and folders when sorting in file tree.
            Add sort by creation time option for file tree / file list.
            File tree view and file list view now is configured separately.
            Increase max line count for global search results.
            Fuzzy search in Open Quickly will now also match folder path.
            Add new math auto numbering rule — AMS Numbering Rules (where only certain environments produce numbered equations, as they would be in LaTeX).
            Add option to always add “./” when generating relative path for images.
            Add rename image in context menu. (Which is the same menu item with move images).
            Improve Pascal lang support, add more keyword highlight for Pascal.
            Add syntax support for Smarty.
            Improve performance when using find function and prevent hangs.
            Make search result more readable compared to ==highlight== texts.
            Increase max col count in table edit UI.
            Recognize .qmd as markdown file.
            Now user can select multiple cols and apply text align from table tool tip all at once.
          Fix
            Fix bugs about switching files.
            Fix triple click on code block.
            Fix code block height not auto changed when enter or exit fullscreen mode on macOS.
            Make font color of completed task more readable in dark themes
            Fix some rendering issue for mermaidjs.
            Remove unnecessary horizontal scroll bar on side bar.
            Fix undo deleted file not displayed in file tree view.
            Fix error when switch files.
            Fix hint behavior when hover on folders of sidebar menu.
            Use smaller margin between math block and normal paragraphs.
            Fix compatibility issues when search with Tai.
            PDF export now supports headers or footers contains non-ASSIC code when export.
            Improve image export quantity.
            Fix PDF export not working on Windows when user account contains special characters.
            Fix epub export show warnings in epub reader when contains video tag
            Fix page size setting of PDF not working on macOS when export.
            Fix the setting of margin right and margin left of PDF not correctly applied when export.
            Fix last export path not saved on macOS.
            Fix docx import fail on newer pandoc versions.
            Fix replace may ignore search results matches with regular expressions contains non-capture groups.
            Fix move images not working for windows.
            Improve performance when md file contains video tag.
            Fix a caret jump issue when typing after inline math.
            Fix minor issues with spellcheck.
            Fix load image with src contains escaped @ mark.
            Fix save-as sometimes not popped up on diagrams.
            Update language translations.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.3.6" date="2022-06-12">
      <description>
        <p>
          New / Improvements
            Support copy / move / download all images.
            Add advanced copy / paste action in context menu.
            Support regular expression in file search, find and replace.
            Show match counts in find and replace panel.
            Support auto move image folder when move or rename current opened markdown document.
            Support ${currentFolder} as export command variable.
            Add Hindi language support.
          Fix
            Fix window content not displayed under macOS ventura.
            Update translations for Chinese, Polish, Slovenian, Spanish, Arabic, Indonesian, Portuguese, etc.
            Update image and math for replace operation, fix search with html entities.
            Fix learned word not kept in some cases (Window / Linux).
            Support abbreviation like (e.g.) is always marked as misspelled in Window / Linux.
            Reduce laggy when editing file with large set of math expressions.
            Do not auto capitalize words after and inside inline math.
            Fix some bugs about text selection.
            Fix poster support for video element.
            Fix live rendering for footnote.
            Fix parsing rules about hr in lists.
            Fix copy table header may include control elements.
            Fix display issue for code block line number when window resize and export.
            Fix issues about open links to other file with anchor position.
            Fix select line at first char of line.
            Keep unicode quote when import.
            Fix context menu for code fences.
            Fix PDF export pay produce empty page as the last page.
            Other bug fix and performance improvement
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.4" date="2022-03-27">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix unnecessary scroll for files with large set of images (macOS).
          Fix sometimes image load fail when root path is set.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.3" date="2022-03-23">
      <description>
        <p>
          New / Improvements
            Upgrade mermaid version
            Support image move operation.
            Support image delete operation.
            Add new image uploader -- Picsee. (macOS)
            Improve macOS performance when document contains large image set
            Add option to reload all images, undo image copy operation will do remove the copied image file.
            Add default shortcut for task list.
            Add syntax highlight for `dart`, `python` and `sql`.
            Added `py` as alias of `python`, `docker` as alias of `dockerfile` for code fences.
            Improve utf8 encode detection on Windows / Linux..
            Slightly improve context menu UI for Windows / Linux.
            Update i18n translations.
          Fix
            Fix some typo at the welcome page.
            Fix an issue that `title` not displayed for reference link.
            Fix `reveal in sidebar` not working when global search is displayed.
            Fix some issues relates to unnecessary scroll when code fences is involved.
            Fix delete folder in sidebar throw permission errors on Windows.
            Fix a bug that "Export in process" not hide when you cancel the export operation.
            Other bug fixes.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.5" date="2022-02-21">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix issues when canceling a saving process.
          Improve undo when auto save is enabled.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.4" date="2022-02-20">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix display issue under languages including Indonesian, French, Catalan and Traditional Chinese.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.3" date="2022-02-19">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix
            Fix a critical issue that some file cannot be opened.
            Fix settings for epub cannot be shown in preferences panel.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.1.2" date="2022-02-17">
      <description>
        <p>
          New / Improvements
            Add Malay language support.
            Add Slovenian language support.
            Fix typo and update translations in other languages.
            Allow create file when open non-exist file via command line.
            Allow create file when open target link that does not have existing file.
            Allow open other files' anchor position directly via file link.
            More compact context menu under Windows / Linux.
            Support copy / cut while line when nothing is selected.
            Add option to disable or enable physics package.
            Allow pasting markdown with Command-Option-Shift-V on macOS.
            Support offline activation and provide web UI to manage used license code.
            Sign Windows executables and installers.
            Support default / theme font size for exported image.
            Ensure downloaded image has image file extension.
            Support loading local image files with user append hashes.
          Fix
            Fix security issue which may cause XSS.
            Fix custom font size for exported image.
            Fix multiple BOM be added when saving files with BOM header.
            Fix copy as MathML not working for math block.
            Fix math auto numbering get wrongly numbered labels.
            Fix file tree UI under smaller customer font size.
            Fix always on top cannot be turned off under macOS.
            Fix image corrupted if your Typora is zoomed.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.4" date="2022-01-11">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix check update failure.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.3" date="2021-12-01">
      <description>
        <p>
          Add option to allow connect to activation server in China.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.2" date="2021-11-27">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix activation process on some older macOS version.
          Fix indent on lists.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2021-11-23">
      <description>
        <p>
          Support YAML front matters (0.8.5), LaTeX math (0.8.7), [toc] (0.9.2), many new code syntax highlights, subscript and superscript (0.9.6), underline (0.9.7), highlight (0.9.8.7), diagrams (0.9.9.7) , local file link (0.9.9.8.2), table editing (0.9.9.8.8), HTML (0.9.9.17), etc...
          Improve editing user experience, support auto pair (0.9.8.7), smart punctuation (0.9.9.16).
          Launched Theme Gallery (0.9.9.7.8) and Support Website.
          Provide outline view (0.9.2), word count (0.9.5), focus mode and typewriter mode (0.9.9.6), dark themes (0.9.9.9.2).
          Provide Typora in other languages (start from 0.9.9.11.2) and spellcheck support.
          File management, including "Open Quickly" (0.9.9.0), file tree / list (0.9.9.10), options when launch (0.9.9.15), global search (0.9.9.20), etc.
          Better image management, include supporting relative path (0.9.4), image copy-to (0.9.9.18) and upload operations (0.9.9.32).
          More advanced export functions (0.10.6).
          New design of preferences panel(0.9.9.27), new icon (0.10.6), and many new themes.
          And much more...
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.18" date="2021-11-17">
      <description>
        <p>
          Add warnings when user try to edit file from backup location.
          Line break should be rendered as whitespace when ignore line break is enabled.
          Fix new file in tile tree will result to duplicate files.
          Fix bug that table with tabs cannot be correct parsed.
          Fix inline math preview issue.
          Fix bug that users cannot jump from some internal links.
          Fix some cursor issue.
          Fix Greek language spellcheck on older Windows and Linux.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.16" date="2021-11-07">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix keys not work in code block sometimes.
          Fix some regression bugs.
          Add basic syntax highlight for htaccess and improve js syntax highlight support.
          Fix math label link not working when auto numbering is disabled.
          Fix header after table not recognized correctly.
          Add option to allow physics package to redefined `\div` macro in math.
          Fix find and replace do not keep previous state in new search.
          Fix sometimes that images using a same name when paste from web.
          Fix file auto refresh not working.
          Other bug fix and improvements.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.15" date="2021-11-06">
      <description>
        <p>
          Add basic syntax highlight for htaccess and improve js syntax highlight support.
          Fix math label link not working when auto numbering is disabled.
          Fix header after table not recognized correctly.
          Add option to allow physics package to redefined `\div` macro in math.
          Fix find and replace do not keep previous state in new search.
          Fix sometimes that images using a same name when paste from web.
          Fix file auto refresh not working.
          Other bug fix and improvements.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.14" date="2021-10-28">
      <description>
        <p>
          N/A
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.13" date="2021-10-18">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix error dialog when open multiple Typora instance.
          Improve inline code parse rule.
          Reduce lag when using IME.
          Fix upload all images fail when image path are escaped.
          Fix connections to resources from some https websites will fail.
          Update i18n translations for Russian, Hungarian, Chinese and Polish.
          Add option to allow physics package to redefine some TeX commands.
          Other bug fix and improvements.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.12" date="2021-10-15">
      <description>
        <p>
          Improve inline code parse rule.
          Reduce lag when using IME.
          Fix upload all images fail when image path are escaped.
          Fix connections to resources from some https websites will fail.
          Update i18n translations for Russian, Hungarian, Chinese and Polish.
          Add option to allow physics package to redefine some TeX commands.
          Other bug fix and improvements.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.8" date="2021-08-31">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix strong not rendered in some cases.
          Fix cursor jump in some cases.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.7" date="2021-08-26">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix issue on save.
          Fix render issue on mermaid diagram.
          Fix parsing issues about strong and emphasis.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.6" date="2021-08-26">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix issue on save.
          Fix render issue on mermaid diagram.
          Fix parsing issues about strong and emphasis.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.5" date="2021-08-16">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix sidebar keeps loading on Linux.
          Fix editing bugs on links and math.
          Fix math style in exported PDF.
          Fix context menu not working on source code mode.
          Add nim, solidity code syntax support.
          Fix bug that cannot embed YouTube videos.
          Fix copy content not copy images as configured.
          Other bug fix.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.2" date="2021-07-24">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix issue about math editing.
          Fix issue about copying image.
          Fix issue about check updates.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.1" date="2021-07-23">
      <description>
        <p>
          Added option to auto apply displaylines environment in math to support line break using \\.
          Fix some bugs.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.11.0" date="2021-07-20">
      <description>
        <p>
          Add shortcut key info on context menu.
          Fix background on Windows start menu tile.
          On Windows unibody style, users can right click on menu icon or use `Alt` + `(E)dit`, `Alt` + `(P)aragraph`, `Alt` + `F(o)rmat`, etc key combinations to open main menu.
          Add menu item to control whether to append final new line or not.
          YAML Front matters now supports ending with three dots (…),
          Code Fences now is better GFM / CommonMark compatible. You can put extra `` ` or `~` to warp code block which contains ``` or ~~~.
          Typora now follows GFM / CommonMark to parse `1)` as ordered list.
          Use GFM compatible tables, leading or trailing pipes are optional in table rows.
          Export will now display warning if it succeeded but with warnings.
          Upgrade to MathJax 3.2 for math faster and better math rendering.
          Support TeX comands from cases, centernot, colortbl, empheq, gensymb, mathtools, textcomp, upgreek, braket, physics, xypic packages.
          Upgrade flowchart version, which supports named branches.
          Add Romanian interface.
          Support undo when converting smart quotes / dashes when input.
          Other bugs fix and improvements.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.10.11" date="2021-05-23">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix issue about save file dialog.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.10.10" date="2021-05-16">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix issue about emoji autocomplete.
          Fix rename issue on file sidebar.
          Keep final newline if original file end with linebreak.
          Fix the issue that may cause Typora window not showing up.
          Other small fix.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.10.9" date="2021-05-09">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix bug for editing issue after images.
          Fix bug that images get updated twice.
          Update Brazilian, Polish, Catalan, and Portuguese translations.
          Fix bug that math block cannot get delete.
          Fix bug that ctrl + backspace may cause cursor gone.
          Other small fix.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.10.7" date="2021-05-02">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix small UI issues.
          Fix text editing bug which may remove texts after link.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.10.6" date="2021-04-28">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix print error.
          Fix image auto upload.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.10.4" date="2021-04-28">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix cursor in inline math.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.10.3" date="2021-04-26">
      <description>
        <p>
          New Typora Icon.
          Improve UI for context menu and fences code language auto complete.
          Add Export options and enhance export functionality.
          Support header, footer and page option for PDF export.
          Support outline sidebar, custom contents and theme for HTML export.
          Support custom font size and width for image export.
          Support table with one row.
          Auto adding table rows on tab key.
          Add Hebrew interface by [Alon](github.com/RealA10N).
          Support configs for diagrams.
          Support anchor links to title with duplicated names.
          Support installation without admin privilege.
          Rename “Move to Trash” to “Delete” for easier understanding.
          Other bugs fix and stability improvements.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.98" date="2020-12-13">
      <description>
        <p>
          Fix regression bugs.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.97" date="2020-12-12">
      <description>
        <p>
          Add vlang and forth code syntax highlight.
          Add “Properties” in context menu for file on Windows.
          Improve markdown parse logic.
          Improve UI and built-in themes.
          Improve compatibility with IMEs.
          Fix print may popup no printer available error.
          Fix open link with escaped urls.
          Fix some mermaid dialog bugs.
          Other bug fix.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.9.96" date="2020-09-14">
      <description>
        <p>
          N/A
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
